Jack Benny papers, 1930-1974
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television scripts.
  - The Jack Benny Program [Lucky Strike].
    - ., February 11, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - ., February 18, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - ., February 25, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - ., March 4, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - ., March 11, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - ., March 18, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - ., March 25, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - ., April 1, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - ., April 29, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - ., May 6, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - ., May 13, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - ., May 20, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - ., May 27, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - ., September 30, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - ., October 7, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - ., October 21, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - ., October 28, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - ., November 4, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - ., November 11, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - ., November 18, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - ., November 25, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - ., December 2, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - ., December 9, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - ., December 16, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - ., December 23, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - ., December 30, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - ., January 6, 1946. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - ., January 13, 1946. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - ., January 20, 1946. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - ., January 27, 1946. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - ., February 3, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - ., March 10, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - ., March 17, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - ., March 24, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - ., March 31, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - ., April 14, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - ., April 21, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - ., April 28, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - ., May 5, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - ., May 12, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - ., May 19, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - ., May 26, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - ., September 29, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - ., October 6, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - ., October 13, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - ., October 20, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - ., October 27, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - ., November 3, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - ., November 10, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - ., November 17, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - ., November 24, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - ., December 1, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - ., December 8, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - ., December 15, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - ., December 22, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - ., December 29, 1946. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - ., January 5, 1947. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - ., January 12, 1947. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - ., January 19, 1947. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - ., January 26, 1947. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - ., February 2, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - ., February 9, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - ., February 16, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - ., February 23, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - ., March 2, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - ., March 9, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - ., March 16, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - ., March 23, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - ., March 30, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - ., April 6, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - ., April 13, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - ., April 20, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - ., April 27, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - ., May 4, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - ., May 11, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - ., May 18, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - ., May 25, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - ., October 5, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - ., October 12, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - ., October 19, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - ., October 26, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - ., November 2, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - ., November 9, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - ., November 16, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - ., November 23, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - ., November 30, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - ., December 7, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - ., December 14, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - ., December 21, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - ., December 28, 1947. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - ., January 4, 1948. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - ., January 11, 1948. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - ., January 18, 1948. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - ., January 25, 1948. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - ., February 1, 1948. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - ., February 8, 1948. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - ., February 15, 1948. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - ., February 29, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ., March 7, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ., March 14, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ., March 21, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ., March 28, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ., April 4, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ., April 25, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ., May 2, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ., May 9, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ., May 16, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ., May 23, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ., May 30, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ., June 6, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ., June 13, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ., June 20, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ., June 27, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ., October 3, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ., October 10, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ., October 17, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ., October 24, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ., October 31, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ., November 7, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ., November 14, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ., November 21, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ., November 28, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ., December 5, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ., December 12, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ., December 19, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ., December 26, 1948. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ., January 2, 1949. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ., January 9, 1949. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ., January 16, 1949. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ., January 23, 1949. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ., January 30, 1949. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ., February 13, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ., February 20, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ., February 27, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ., March 6, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ., March 13, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ., March 20, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ., March 27, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ., April 3, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ., April 10, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ., April 17, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ., April 24, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ., May 1, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ., May 8, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ., May 15, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ., May 22, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ., May 29, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ., September 11, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ., September 25, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ., October 2, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ., October 9, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ., October 16, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ., October 23, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ., October 30, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ., November 6, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ., November 13, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ., November 20, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ., November 27, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ., December 4, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ., December 11, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ., December 18, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ., December 25, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ., January 1, 1950. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ., January 8, 1950. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ., January 15, 1950. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ., January 22, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - ., January 29, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - ., February 5, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - ., February 12, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - ., February 19, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - ., February 26, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - ., March 5, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - ., March 12, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - ., March 19, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - ., April 9, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - ., April 16, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - ., April 23, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - ., April 30, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - ., May 7, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - ., May 14, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - ., May 21, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - ., May 28, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - ., September 10, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - ., September 17, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - ., September 24, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - ., October 1, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - ., October 8, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - ., October 15, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - ., October 27, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - ., October 29, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - ., November 5, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - ., November 12, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ., November 19, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ., November 26, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ., December 3, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ., December 10, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ., December 17, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ., December 24, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ., December 31, 1950. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ., January 21, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - ., January 28, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - ., February 4, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - ., February 11, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - ., February 18, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - ., February 25, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - ., March 4, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - ., March 18, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - ., March 25, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ., April 1, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ., April 8, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ., April 15, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ., April 22, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ., April 29, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ., May 6, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ., May 13, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ., May 20, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ., May 27, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ., June 3, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ., September 16, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - ., September 23, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - ., September 30, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - ., October 7, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - ., October 14, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - ., October 21, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - ., October 28, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - ., November 4, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - ., November 11, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - ., November 18, 1951. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - ., November 25, 1951. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - ., December 2, 1951. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - ., December 9, 1951. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - ., December 16, 1951. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - ., December 23, 1951. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - ., December 30, 1951. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - ., January 6, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - ., January 13, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - ., January 20, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - ., February 3, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - ., February 10, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - ., February 17, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - ., February 24, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - ., March 2, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - ., March 9, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - ., March 16, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - ., March 23, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - ., March 30, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - ., March 6, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - ., March 13, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - ., March 20, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - ., March 27, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - ., May 4, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - ., May 11, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - ., May 18, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - ., May 25, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - ., June 1, 1952. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - ., September 14, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - ., September 21, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - ., September 28, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - ., October 5, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - ., October 12, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - ., October 19, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - ., October 26, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - ., November 2, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - ., November 9, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - ., November 16, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ., November 23, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ., November 30, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ., December 7, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ., December 11, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ., December 21, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ., December 28, 1952. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ., January 4, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ., January 11, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ., January 18, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ., January 25, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ., February 1, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ., February 8, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ., February 15, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ., February 22, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ., March 1, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ., March 8, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ., March 15, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ., March 22, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ., March 29, 1953. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ., April 5, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ., April 12, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ., April 19, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ., April 26, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ., May 3, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ., May 10, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ., May 17, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ., May 24, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ., May 31, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ., June 7, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ., September 13, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ., September 20, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ., September 27, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ., October 4, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ., October 11, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ., October 18, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ., October 25, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ., November 1, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ., November 8, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ., November 15, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ., November 22, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ., November 29, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ., December 6, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ., December 13, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ., December 20, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ., December 27, 1953. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ., January 3, 1954. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ., January 10, 1954. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ., January 17, 1954. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ., January 24, 1954. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ., January 31, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ., February 7, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ., February 14, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ., February 21, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ., February 28, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ., March 7, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ., March 14, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ., March 21, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ., March 28, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ., April 4, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ., April 11, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ., April 18, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ., April 25, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ., May 2, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ., May 9, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ., May 16, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ., May 23, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ., May 30, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ., June 6, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ., September 26, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - ., October 3, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - ., October 10, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - ., October 17, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - ., October 24, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - ., October 31, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - ., November 7, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - ., November 14, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - ., November 21, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - ., November 28, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ., December 5, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ., December 12, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ., December 19, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ., December 26, 1954. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ., January 2, 1955. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ., January 9, 1955. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ., January 16, 1955. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ., January 23, 1955. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ., February 6, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - ., February 13, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - ., February 20, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - ., February 27, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - ., March 6, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - ., March 13, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - ., March 20, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - ., March 27, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - ., April 3, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - ., April 10, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - ., April 17, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - ., April 24, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - ., May 1, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - ., May 8, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - ., May 15, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - ., May 22, 1955. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Special programs:. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - --Burns and Allen, Maxwell House Coffee Time.., November 29, 1945. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - -- Pabst Blue Ribbon Show.., October 26, 1945. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - --Lady Esther Screen Guild Players, Parent by Proxy.., January 13, 1946. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - --Rodger Young Village dedication.., April 27, 1946. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - --Elgin Show.., November 28, 1946. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - --Glamour Manor.., January 20, 1947. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - --The Fitch Bandwagon, Phil Harris and Alice Faye.., March 9, 1947. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - --19th Academy Award presentations.., March 13, 1947. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - --Salute to Volunteers, Community Chest Program.., September 27, 1947. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - --Elgin Show spot.., November 27, 1947. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - --The Fitch Bandwagon, Phil Harris and Alice Faye.., December 21, 1947. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - --George Burns and Gracie Allen.., January 8, 1948. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - -- The Bob Hope Show.., December 9, 1948. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - --Anacin Hollywood Star Theatre.., November 13, 1948. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - --The Hallmark Playhouse, My financial career.., November 18, 1948. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - --Elgin Thanksgiving Show.., November 25, 1948. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - -- Sealtest Variety Theatre.., December 9, 1948. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - -- The Eddie Cantor Show.., December 17, 1948. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - -- The Phil Harris-Alice Faye Show.., December 19, 1948. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - --Lucky Strike, Incorporated, Jack Benny Program, experimental program #1.., December 22, 1948. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - -- Bob Crosby Show, Club 15 spot.., December 1948. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - --Disc jockey spot, interview with Benny.., n.d. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - -- The Gene Autry Show.., January 1, 1949. (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - --Campfire Girls Birthday Salute.., March 16, 1949. (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - -- Maxwell House Coffee Time, Burns & Allen.., March 31, 1949. (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - --Louella Parsons broadcast.., April 3, 1949. (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - --Treasury Department, bond spot.., May 8, 1949. (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - --Light Up Time.., September 14, 1949. (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - -- The Bob Hope Show.., December 6, 1949. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Broadcasts from Palm Springs:.
    - ., February 23, 1941. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - ., March 2, 1941. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - ., March 9, 1941. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - ., November 29, 1942. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - ., November 14, 1943. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - ., April 8, 1945. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - ., April 22, 1945. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - ., February 10, 1946. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - ., February 17, 1946. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ., February 24, 1946. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ., March 3, 1946. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ., February 22, 1948. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ., April 11, 1948. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ., April 18, 1948. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ., March 26, 1950. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ., April 2, 1950. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - The Jack Benny Television Show.
    - ., October 28, 1950. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ., January 28, 1951. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ., April 1, 1951. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ., May 20, 1951. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ., November 4, 1951. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - ., December 16, 1951. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - ., January 27, 1952. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - ., March 9, 1952. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - ., April 20, 1952. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - ., October 5, 1952. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - ., November 2, 1952. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - ., November 30, 1952. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - ., December 28, 1952. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - ., January 25, 1953. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - ., March 22, 1953. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - ., April 19, 1953. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - ., May 17, 1953. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - ., September 13, 1953. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - ., October 4, 1953. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - ., October 25, 1953. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - ., November 15, 1953. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - ., December 6, 1953. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - ., December 27, 1953. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - ., January 17, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - ., February 7, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - ., February 28, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - ., March 21, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - ., April 11, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - ., May 2, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - ., May 23, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - ., October 3, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - ., October 17, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - ., October 31, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - ., November 14, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - ., November 28, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - ., December 12, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - ., December 26, 1954. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - ., January 23, 1955. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - ., February 6, 1955. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - ., February 20, 1955. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - ., March 6, 1955. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - ., March 20, 1955. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - ., April 3, 1955. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - ., April 17, 1955. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - ., May 1, 1955. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - ., September 25, 1955. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ., October 9, 1955. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ., October 23, 1955. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ., November 6, 1955. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ., November 20, 1955. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ., December 4, 1955. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ., December 18, 1955. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ., January 1, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ., January 15, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ., January 29, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ., February 12, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - ., February 26, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - ., March 11, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - ., March 25, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - ., April 8, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - ., April 22, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - ., September 23, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - ., October 7, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - ., October 21, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - ., November 4, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - ., November 18, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - ., December 16, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - ., December 30, 1956. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - ., January 13, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - ., January 27, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - ., February 10, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - ., February 24, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - ., March 24, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - ., April 21, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - --repeat telecast of May 11, 1956.., March 5, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - --repeat telecast of February 26, 1956.., May 19, 1956. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - --repeat telecast of January 15, 1956.., June 2, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - --repeat telecast of November 6, 1955.., June 16, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - ., September 22, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - ., October 6, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - ., October 20, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - ., November 3, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - ., November 17, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - ., December 1, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - ., December 15, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - ., December 29, 1957. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - ., January 12, 1958. (Box 46, Folder 4)